RUIWEN ZHOU RESUME

▶ Full name: Ruiwen Zhou **▶ Gender:** Male

▶ Native place: Ningde, Fujian
▶ Nation: Han

▶ Date of birth: 2000.09
▶ Major: Information Engineering



Education

2018.09 - present Graduating as Bachelor in Information Engineering Shanghai Jiao Tong University

Description of the November 2 / 100, Ranking: 2 / 149

2020.02 - present Minoring in Computer Science and Engineering Shanghai Jiao Tong University

▶ Overall Grade: 93.17 / 100, No ranking info. for minor

Experience

2021.01 - present Student Researcher at Single-agent RL Group, APEX Guided by Prof. Weinan Zhang

▶ Imitation learning, Model-based RL

2019.10 - 2021.01 Student Researcher at Crowdsourcing Group, DCE Guided by Prof. Xiaofeng Gao

▶ Spatial crowdsourcing, Combinatorial optimization

Projects & Researches

2021.05 - 2021.06	Data Mining and Predicting on AceMap	EE226 Course Project
2021.02 - 2021.04	Multi-agent Imitation Learning Benchmark	Multi-agent RL, APEX
2020.05 - 2020.06	Control by Imitation Learning for 2048 Game	EE228 Course Project
2020.02 - 2021.02	Task Assignment in Mobile Crowdsourcing	PRP of CSS, DCE

Honors & Awards

2021.04	Outstanding Winner, ICM 2021-D	2020.04	Meritorious Winner, MCM 2020-C
2020.12	Zhiyuan Honor Scholarship	2019.12	Tung OOCL Scholarship
2020.11	National Scholarship	2019.12	Zhiyuan Honor Scholarship
2020.11	A-level Excellent Scholarship	2019.11	B-level Excellent Scholarship
2020.10	Merit Student		

Summary

I am Ruiwen Zhou, a third-year undergraduate student in SEIEE, Shanghai Jiao Tong University. I am now pursuing the bachelor's degree at the department of electronic engineering, and I also minor in computer science and technology. My research mainly focuses on topics related to machine learning, especially imitation learning and single-agent reinforcement learning.

I always feel excited and highly-motivated about the theory and application of machine learning, and I actively participate in relevant projects and discussions. I also have decent English listening and writing skill. My major weaknesses are that I am a little introverted and sometimes not very confident about myself, but I am always trying to overcome them and becoming better.